A person named Yeongho Chaek
On the ice with people under the ice
I dreamed of talking
May fortune teller Saekdam interpret the dream.
Sheep on ice
Under the ice is yin, so yin and yang
That is, it is about men and women
you are a matchmaker
When the ice melts
There will be a ceremony
Jinseo Art Exhibition Glacier Story
It was sent by Samshin.
How have you been?
Wolha Elderly
Our three gods have ruled
This is their list
It just worked out well.
So where should we try to make some flowers bloom?
Wow, is this a fate painting?
But why are some flowers white?
Which flowers are red?
The connection is
Although it is originally white
People who are connected with Hong Yeon
When we get to know each other
It's in full bloom red
Ah
But
Why are only those flowers different colors?
When a person is born
Everyone is born with their own destiny.
The people we are destined for are hand in hand
Connected by a red thread
Finding out about my relationship
The thread is called Hongyeon.
Those connected to Hongyeon
No matter what hardships and trials come
We will meet in the end
No matter how many laps I spin
If not in this life
Even in the next life, definitely
Wow, then Hongyeon
Everyone wins, right?
no
Protecting my relationship is
Much worse than I thought
It's a difficult task.
There are worse things in this world than you think
There are many bad people
Lady Seo!
Then it's so hard
Why are you giving it to me?
love
Even if I can’t win them all
Because it makes people strong
That's how I connect with people
This is the reason we are together
The owners of those flowers too
pretty
We met each other a long time ago
I heard you had a relationship
Huh, you know what?
If you catch the falling petals
They say first love comes true
Really? Wow
Who is your first love?
huh?
- Oh, I-I'm not really.
- It's a secret.
If it's Hongyeon's will,
The two must have been happy for a long time
human greed
If I hadn't intervened
It will be shattered like this
Something like a tragedy
wouldn't have happened
degradation
Have you had a nightmare?
I had a very bad dream
It's so bad that poverty disappears
Poverty...
Uh, low
Deterioration
ha
What happened to this dragon gun?
I knew it would be like this, I
Yes? In Gonryongpo
Is there any problem?
huh? give it to me
What if I ask back?
Do you see that or not?
‘Personal color type’
People have innate colors
You have to wear clothes that suit you
The face is alive
I'm really alive
Until I wear out this precious mouth
I told you
I know it well.
Jeoha's personal color type matches the Habing type.
As you said last time,
With red lining
I finished it
What else are you having trouble with?
This lining, huh? This lining!
That red...
Is it the right color?
This is suitable for Seolhwa type
It's not bright red
The lining that suits me is
softer than this
How many times do I say red, huh?
This ice and snowflake
It's completely different.
Vernal and autumn leaf types
It's an indistinguishable coincidence, huh?
Yes, I'm sorry.
30 years of conviction
It was sent by the upper house, but
Among the previous kings and crown princes,
People looking for that type
No, you were there
I'm very immature
I created a personal color pattern
It's been five years since I told you
When was Taryeong in his days?
Please kill me
degradation
Oh my, oh my
If people don't know
I should think about learning, ugh.
Do you write if you think about dying first?
I admitted that I was immature.
Personal color type halved
While working on segmenting
Focus more on your sense of beauty
That
Break it down further, okay?
Uh, half again over there?
Why don't you like it?
If you do this, I will cut your torso.
Should I pay half, huh?
No
degradation
Seong Eun-i
I'm devastated...
Clothes should become wings
If this beauty becomes the wings of clothes
It's not possible
Hey
Now
Let's do it with you today
degradation
Is it right to hasten the national wedding?
What is more important than national marriage
It is to carry on the legacy of Sajik of Jongmyo Shrine.
If there is no suitable resource for poverty,
At least bring in a concubine.
Ai, Do Seung-ji
What does that mean?
There is no Crown Princess, so why bring in a concubine?
And the wife's food and
My husband and I are talking about marriage.
Are you saying you don't have the right materials?
Haha, the Gyesa-nyeon incident
don't forget
On one day, His Majesty the King and his valence
When you said goodbye
The King Seon Seon’s second daughter.
Because His Majesty the Lord was there
Resignation from Jongmyo Shrine without confusion
I was able to continue
The prosperity of the royal family
The prosperity of the country comes soon.
Please pass on the succession as soon as possible
Please stabilize Joseon.
Now that means
His Majesty the Lord and His Majesty the Lord
Are you saying you are going to die suddenly?
Lee Pandaegam
Where did you get such a leap?
Well, isn’t that a bit harsh?
What, are you using a point with a pointer?
How old is Do Seung-ji?
Are you this rude?
I have had enough.
It's my year of the rat.
I am Byeongjinnyeon Yong!
After a long time, the young author
Such a byeongjin bitch, Mr.
What, what bitch, bitch, bitch?
Because I don’t know the elder Byeongjinnyeon.
I'm sorry
Well, let's give it a try now.
What, now, huh?
Well, I can't say that
None, now
Oh, this little guy now
Huh? ah
Oh, don't worry about me
Just keep doing what you were doing
That, originally
It's a mess
Hey, something like this
Because it tastes good when you chew it.
Month!
month!
Dear, ministers
Are you making fun of me?
No matter how harsh this may be,
That joke is so, so
I think you went too far.
um
Wow
Left, left, left, left
no, not me
Shouldn’t you aim over there?
This is Kim Ja-kyung.
My 5th cousin, Ja-kyung.
Bondi
The Prime Minister is not good at guarding those around him.
A law that deserves to be broken down
Cut out the tongue of this unfaithful man.
I apologize to you
Oh, do you want to do that, then?
low, low, low, low
- Left, Captain Left!
- child
That's it.
That not-so-pretty tongue
How about cutting it into one piece?
The loyalty of my left counterpart is
Because I know it well
Just put away your sword.
Ugh, I'm devastated.
degradation
If you do not doubt the integrity of your beliefs
He quickly issued a ban on marriage,
according to appropriate procedures
Have a national wedding
No, it's a ban or a procedure.
What does it matter?
The Crown Princess did what was decided
Isn’t that the seat of Assessa?
Isn’t Mr. Eo an unexpected person?
Who is there?
What?
I'm sorry.
Who is the ruler?
May I ask you a question?
No, you don't know the location?
Oh my
Well, it's because I don't have any sense, won
Assess position
‘Anyway, the Crown Princess is a sitting woman’
my heart already
I ate it like that
I issued a ban on marriage.
Your wife and crown prince
hold a national wedding
If you give birth to your first child,
Are you planning to kill the crown prince?
Or make you crazy like me
Are you going to lock him in the back room?
You are exaggerating, Your Majesty.
ha
'Nong'...
This is what you are doing now
Does it look like fur?
yes
I said nong
I'm deaf.
Also, I
Your Majesty said that the Okche is immature.
Your Majesty is Okche Miryeong.
Also
I am crazy about your Majesty
They said it got worse
Your Majesty cannot take care of government affairs.
This is the status
Strain injury!
So why
Did you really want to become a king?
Oh my, are they
Why did it get so big?
Originally a goldfish
Depending on where you live
It is a fish whose size increases endlessly.
Is that so?
'Is that so?'
Ha, hey
I'm sure the things that breathe in the water
I ordered them all to be killed.
As you can see, that little thing
Looks like your face has opened up a bit?
Do you know a goldfish?
That's actually
Raised at the Great King’s Vision,
It's a goldfish
Mama told me to throw it away
Even if it's just a small thing
There is life
I can't just let him die...
Please kill me, you!
Don't ask me to kill you carelessly.
Especially when I'm by the water
That goldfish
I breathe and jump around in the water, but
People
If you go into the water, you will suffocate and die.
If left for a long time
It swells and crumbles.
Here
Even if you just touch it with your fingers
Kill me, no...
Oh, please forgive me
Please be like Hahae
Please give me grace
Please forgive the girl
I hope you reach Gyeonghaengrok
‘Extend your loyalty widely’
Where do people live
Why don't we meet?
So
I will be loyal to you
Seong-eun is devastated.
However, myeongmyeongbogam
By transcribing
I won't ask you about your sins
Yes?
After the deceased passed away
You are alive in the water
hates everything
I paid close attention to you
Thank goodness it ended with transcription.
Well, if you are a destitute person
Due to the assassination of Joongjeonmama,
Didn't you receive the medicine?
But that's water and
What does it matter?
The deceased received a blessing, but
claiming innocence
threw myself into the water
Left unattended for a long time
So much so that I can't even recognize your face
a decayed body
You checked it yourself
So I can only resent the water.
Things running around in it
It's bound to be hateful
Absolutely poor
There is no way I could commit suicide.
Someone killed the poor man
It's disguised as suicide.
Please be free from poverty
Please reveal
It is true that poverty committed suicide.
Why on earth!
for what reason
Are you saying that poverty leads to suicide?
I
ordered
What is that...
If poverty is alive
you hold the child's hand
They'll try to run away
If you give a curse to the poor,
You are the one who will drink that poison instead.
So I ordered
die for you
my mother and poverty
You are protected by the blood of my father-in-law.
Don't forget the weight of my life
I never wanted it
Who is death for?
I'm already completely broken
Who did they die for?
I'm already dead
Abama killed me.
It was very cold, right?
You were very scared, right?
Don't worry anymore
I will cover it soon
Why...
Why!
Still needs to be degraded
So buy it now
If I say it is now
At that time, you just have to give up your life.
That's it
This is the new law of this palace.
Do you think I will do as you wish?
your girl's meal
Let him sit in an empty palace
Let those veins sit on the throne
Do you think I will obey obediently?
It should be like that.
To do that, I killed the heavy warrior.
Because it was put on the poor person.
Now come
Why are you telling me the truth?
If you know the truth
Because nothing will change
No one dares punish me
No, I won't punish you.
Those who will die in place of this Kim Han-cheol
There is spirit in this palace.
So
Instead of revenge,
Didn’t you choose suicide?
weakly
Yes this guy
Yes, you guy!
Like scared anger
There is no one to fear
Weakness is cowardice, force is sin
Be strong
Only the strong are justice in this world
Ouch!
Deterioration, degradation, degradation...
Are you okay?
I'll call the meaning
became
I miss you
fish saiso
Pollack Saiso
Let's eat some fish
There is delicious pollack
I'll pass, eh
Oh, hello, yeah
I'll pass, yeah
Oh my
Ah, ah, it’s been a while since I saw you, ing
Hey, hey, did you eat? Ying
I'm scared of this fish's eyes
Don’t you do business?
Ah, take it easy from earlier.
What are you looking for?
So where can you find the biggest house?
That's the house
Are you there?
What's going on?
Would you like a glass of water? In this big house?
Hey, I drank a lot of water, yeah
Oh, that, and the hares too.
Do you really just drink water?
Oh, do you sell things?
It's a product. Who knows who will buy it?
How could the guy selling it know?
No, you need to know what you're selling
Whether you buy it or not, is there anything you want to do?
Oh, it's okay
I need something
You should have said it already.
Did you drink a lot of water?
Now, wait!
Well...
Want to unpack?
It makes no sense to lose
This salt says it all
Listen carefully.
What? Hey, wow, really
That's why he said that
I am the highest quality salt
If you don't buy me
He's stupid
It's mom
Wow, thank you, ying
Ah!
Oh my gosh, it's salt.
Oh my goodness
Did you sell a lot today?
I emptied the entire jar of salt.
Uh, hey, are you okay?
What are you doing now?
You almost got hurt
Oh my
Did you know?
I know you don't know
I was just trying to let you know.
Why do you say that?
Well, the stone I threw as a joke
The backpacker is hit and falls behind.
Where is that saying?
I don't know if it's a frog
A frog, a wealthy merchant, and a nobleman.
Soft skin is all the same.
- Apologize.
- Uh huh
The lecturer’s laws are solemn.
How could a nobleman treat a lowly backpacker?
Are you saying you apologize?
Hey, I'm so ignorant
I don't know if the lecture method is the same.
Gu Man-yu, who only knows human duties
If you made a mistake
Whether a nobleman or a commoner
I have to apologize
But what, I don’t understand that.
There is only one answer
Hawk is medicine!
Mom, that is
You're a nobleman! Oh, it's mom!
Those little things
He's a nobleman
As an adult, I can endure it!
After all, when life is bitter, this is the best
What is it, huh?
What's wrong with you?
Father
And those noble kids
Chaff that was stoned?
Did you know?
Every time you get upset
The Western merchant gave me
Is it sabun or sabong?
You blow bubbles with that.
It's expensive so my father
I can't blow it once, but you're the only one who blows it.
I need to blow this at least
I feel a little relieved.
I'm not loose, okay?
I guess it won't work, huh?
I mean today
- Oh my.
- You're a nobleman and all, huh?
Lift up your arms, huh?
- About to hit me, huh, huh?
- Okay, come on.
Huh?
That's it
I raised both arms so let’s go
Huh? Well, that's right, no
- Oh my.
- I'm weak from the cold.
Ugh, ugh.
That's it, ugh
I avoid poop because it’s dirty.
Well, do you avoid it because you’re scared?
draw
Draw, well thought out
In everything about this award
If you respond with violence
It can't be done
I just think it's shit
Move on, eh, ok
In this land of Joseon
There's a world of difference between a nobleman, a nobleman, and a nobleman.
A day or two?
station in life? That has a very deep legacy.
By the way
This is what I was born with.
I wish I lived a life of being treated with contempt.
That would work, right?
Tusk, as you know,
I fell into the water a few years ago
This bastard has been completely washed away.
My hair is white and my memories are black
When I opened my eyes, I saw that I was a normal guy.
nobleman, nobleman
I can't even tell the difference.
Are you calling me a normal guy?
I guess I'll get used to this, huh?
- Aren’t you feeling unfair and disgusted?
- okay
Are you feeling sleepy?
kid, yeah
Make money quickly and become a nobleman who buys Gongmyeongcheop.
Don't worry about us for no reason
If you have that money, you can play gonggi
What are you doing with that piece of paper?
burn a lot of money
Ugh
- I
- Huh?
I'm going to make a lot of money and go to the West Country.
hanging
They say all people are equal under heaven?
Yiing
That western country is Yuldo country.
Even in Yuldo country
Hong Gil-dong is the king?
I couldn't call my father father
A bastard founded a country
'Equal awards!'
Talk about it and put it aside
Ji is playing king, right?
That's the way the world is, really.
Why is my only daughter
Break your dreams and build them up
- Aig!
- Oh, why are you hitting me?
- child
Why all the violence, huh?
Ah, ah, well, let's go then, okay?
Seogukga
Before I go
Go to Gunnut Village first
Why are you hanging it?
Uh, uh, you know
An old man who was a naval commander
Yiing, that, old man Heo.
I'll take a look at you
Why is that inspiration looking for me?
Well, you know what mouth is looking for.
I guess Joodaeng knows, right?
This guy needs to go to the temple.
Uh, owner
Oh, that, I keep dreaming
He married in Hanyang
My daughter showed up
I'm shedding tears of blood, oh my
Just at a young age
Is it because I feel sorry for being a widow?
I cried so sadly, I just
No, not long ago
I will follow you to the West after I die.
I even sent this letter.
If your dreams are wild
You need to call a shaman.
Not yet
I'm busy and I'm leaving the sad father-in-law to sit down
Stop spinning around.
It won't work anyway
- Hey, what?
- He told me to go to Hanyang.
Checking on Aggie’s well-being
Aren’t you asking me to come?
If you send a personal letter to someone outside the Buddhist priesthood,
A bastard who will be hated for no reason
He disguised himself as a bangmul seller.
I'm telling you to stop by
No?
Oh, the shaman was here
Ugh, no, yes
Even if you go somewhere else
It will never be as good as Hanyang.
Boy, that person is really, tsk
Please take a look at my situation
child
Money isn't important, really.
No, that precious daughter
I'm shedding bloody tears
I'm so happy
Because this money is not important
Yes, indeed
I never saw people like that.
It's really tight, really.
Oh, those, tears of blood
It flows like a river
I'm so happy
This money, huh?
Although money is not important
The fatherhood of this tearful father
How is it
You pretended not to know, right?
Thank you. Okay.
Oh my, baby
As you write this letter, huh?
So many tears...
Why but?
Wait, what is this?
uh?
Oh my, hey
Oh no
By taking precious time
I'm sorry
What do you mean by that?
Now is the time for me
Don’t you have to convince me?
What should I do?
You can't bring in people who have already left the Buddhist priesthood.
Even if they bring me
Those young people are the people of the world
Can you handle the pointing of a finger?
I just want to live
Why should I point fingers?
People say they want to live as people...
Even if you stop me
I can't get over it this time
I have to save the losing baby.
Stretch out your feet and go to sleep, Mr.
Thank you for your words
After, let's go
- It's the moon.
- Aunt
They said they came today
Are you leaving again?
yes?
Ah, yes
Hey, what are you doing lying in the corner of the room?
I need to make a lot of money
No need to overdo it
Even your adoptive parents
There is no need to consider it a burden.
Well, it's a burden.
Even though it’s heavy when I lift it
I need it all
The big guy you carry on your back
To him
I'm just going to carry it on my back.
It's the moon
Always take care of yourself
Because the scoundrels are still looking for you
You should never go to Hanyang
never
Yes, yes, yes, of course
Don't worry.
I'm going to go to Hanyang
Because I don’t have any
He said he had no where to go.
I didn't say I couldn't go
It's still Boryeong, yeah, yeah
Ugh
By the way, this old man said this
Did you draw it as a map? What is this?
Well, I'd like to ask you something...
ask
Just, hmm
I will ask my heart
What is it?
It just goes
Okay, then
Huh?
No, what does that mean?
No, they say they are banning marriage?
Ah, I, I, I, I
What are you going to do with the room?
Anyway, the nobles
I'm not going to raise the bar.
No, why?
No, that story too
Haven't you heard of it?
Crown Princess and Jungjeon
If only women entered the palace,
I'm not dying
Ugh, really?
What does that mean?
Among our ministers
No one wants to buy anything
You mean you didn't upload it?
Don't you know that?
Anyway, the Crown Princess
I'm going to be the girl on the left
It's obvious that I'll be a bridesmaid or a bridesmaid.
Who would put the Saju Danja in it?
These selfish guys
mama
There is no law that says you have to stand behind the crown prince.
He is the eldest son of His Majesty the late King.
Mama's only bloodline
Isn’t there Prince Jeun?
ha
To the Queen's Queen
Even though he was falsely accused and died
It was also the case that the great prince was dethroned from the crown prince.
It's me
But come now
Stand behind Grand Prince Jean?
When the great general mounts the dragon podium
Not avenging my mother
Where is the guarantee?
No, ma’am...
Prince Jeun is not allowed.
Yes mama
Via Hanyang Sangsang Daehaengsu
Find the woman you deserve
If my person can't be the Crown Princess
Even an atom of my human womb
I have to give birth
Absolutely like that snarky snake
As long as the blood on the left side is the original
I have to stop it
My Majesty, I have decreed a ban on marriage.
I will install a wedding guide.
Do as you wish.
yes, degradation
Also, to the second-ranked family,
I give you a virtuous woman’s money.
Setting an example for others
It looks good
Do as you wish, sir.
Is there anything else you want to say?
Also, do as you wish.
Then today I
I have a schedule
I'll just wake up now
No, I'm sorry.
What schedule are you talking about?
I'm going to Gibang
‘Gibang’?
um
Today, Jeundaegun
I heard you returned from the Qing Dynasty.
I have a debt to pay off
I need to go in and out of the room.
This crazy guy
Living on a whale like this
Do you want to eat your daughter-in-law too?
Damn it
There are more people out there.
Oh no
Are you there!
yes
Ha, what?
This is a room vendor passing by, here.
Uh...
Oh, excuse me
To the criminal who ate my husband
I see Bangmul Merchant, what are you doing?
Because there are a lot of good things
Please at least take a look
That's it, let me out
Yes ma'am
Get out, ah, quickly...
- Get out, get out.
- There are a lot of good things in this.
Ah...
Oh my...
Uh, ah, ah, what should I do?
Oh my god...
Wait a minute
asked
Yes?
Take me to the byeoldang
Yes ma'am
Thank you, ma’am.
Ugh, yeah
Follow me
thank you
Huh, you...
Shhh
Sent by old man Heo
Because of the virtuous woman’s door
Are you forced to commit suicide?
Do you want to live?
ruler! Which one should I choose?
If you are hesitating whether you can choose
don't hesitate
There are a lot of things
Of course you can choose.
No, you have to choose.
Hey
They openly tell me to die
Anyway, read these merchants
Wow, reading comprehension
I take my time
I'll explain
Once you get the item you want
Let's take your pick.
This is for the women of the widow village
This is a popular item.
And this is my aunt
This is a silver sword that I received from Gaekju.
Either that or it came from the Qing
There are also things
I again
I have a lot of connections in the office.
I guess
The first one...
Well thought out
If you do
I'll show you how to use it
Here is how to use it
Good to see
This...
Could you please...
Ah, let me solve it.
Ah, just in my arms
All you have to do is take it
Oh, that's okay then, okay
Ah
It's great to be out here.
You are
You came out to have fun
We also do this
Please stick to the palace for a while.
Why not?
I don't like it, it's dull
This palace and Gonryong grapes
At that point, it becomes dull
I wonder if it's a degradation
I have reasonable doubt...
I am you
Even if I'm buried in this dull ground
I wonder if it will work
I feel reasonably confident.
Oh, my apologies!
Ah, but I also
I have to say what's on my mind
I lost my senses again
How
Yoon Se-dol isn’t coming because of work?
- Come to work.
- Uh, mom, uh, uh!
Come to work
Does this kid want to die?
The color is pretty
um
Hey, cool...
It feels different
um
poverty
degradation
Sir, why are you doing this?
saw my poverty
Will and body
You saw it yourself
Tomb mound
You covered it yourself, but
How can you live in poverty?
It was clearly poverty.
Ha, what
As soon as it arrives, is it a land mine?
huh?
now
Are you looking at me?
There are still scoundrels
I'm looking for you
You should never go to Hanyang
- Why are you working so hard, ah!
- Mom, it's a surprise!
Oh my, hey
- Ah...
- What? Are you really the owner?
- Mr. A
- Oh, this really hurts.
Ugh, it really hurts
I have committed a deadly sin!
Dear Crown Prince! Here, here, here
Here, here, here
Was it truly a welcome?
Wow...
Wham?
Well, is there something like that in this place?
What is it?
Hanyang is different though.
draw
I was too complacent
It's a shame you're not interested, huh? Tsk
A slave who ran away from Hanyang
Just without any sincerity
Please take me away
When I walked around like this
Oh, oh, oh, oh
♪ While the moon was in pursuit ♪
♪ Losing my parents ♪
♪ To the owner in Hanyang ♪
♪ I was chased ♪
♪ Shaba Shaba Ai Shaba ♪
Oh my, shabba, huh?
As soon as I came to Hanyang
Why step on a landmine?
huh?
What is it?
Ah, evil!
Hey!
evil!
Ugh...
Mr. I
Hey
Huh?
this?
Ah, well, well
That's more important, yeah
I'm so happy
Well, the tooth didn't come out.
Wow, I'm out of my mind, tsk.
Wow, what a head.
Wow, the head, um...
Huh?
Um...
Are you okay?
Do you know how worried I was?
Ah...
Wow
It's okay, ow
Where is my luggage? Wow
Oh my
There's a lot going on, right?
Ah, then I'll just lose, ah
Didn't you hear me?
I was worried?
Hey, thank you for your concern, uh
Oh, thank you for this treatment too.
Then you lose, okay?
What if I just go?
What about that?
Oh, it's broken.
It's a waste
Yeah
What is the reaction?
Destroyed my belongings
If you are this calm
What should I do?
Strictly speaking
It wasn't broken.
The one who threw it into the ditch was Nari Indie
I didn't throw it
Did you drop it because you were surprised?
map woman indie
I'm changing my clothes, why are you a black guy?
I'm looking at you like this
I was a little surprised and screamed.
Is that common sense?
That's right
Who holds this precious thing?
Do you want to go up high? It's me
Hahahaha!
haha
Jeokbanhajang, these cheeks I know
I guess two hits is enough.
Jiyu
Even if I want to eat and die, I don’t have that much money.
Just peel off the skin
with winter fabric
If you want to use it, use it, okay?
Even if it's just like that, it will be helpful to my household.
What kind of ugly things did you say to this woman?
Life is a winding minefield.
I have a hard time saying nice words.
So, let me be kind
What are you going to do?
What should I do?
Maybe because of one thing
Are you worried I'll kill you?
Then let's go
Will you forgive me?
Then
compensation
Just do it and that's it
Father
Tusk
Ji Gayu
Where are you going?
until I finish my schedule
wait here
Traveler's father
yes
Yeah
Oh, isn't that strange?
Where have all these silver swords gone?
That
Dal took everything?
- Ying
- No, the kid selling salt.
Why Eunjangdo? And all of that?
Well, Chunhyang
I guess it's a dream
Mongryong
- Oh my.
- Do you want me to cut a pear for you?
child
Now that I think about it,
He went out carrying the salt poison.
salt
You didn't take it?
what?
Mom, oh my, oh my mother
Um, mom, mom, mom
Uh, uh, pear, uh, pear
Mom, what is it?
Oh, wait a minute, oh, that's not working.
Coming out, coming out, ugh...
Ah...
Ugh...
Anyway
How is this a map woman?
I'm doing my business in front of the man.
It won't work
- Ooh, ooh, ooh...
- Oh hey, really.
I won't see you, so don't worry, okay?
Well, yeah
No, why does this sound, why...
Are you pooping in the bed again?
Oh, really?
Hello shit
Seriously, where is the lie?
You come out when you feel like it, ugh.
Yes, for reference
This is 10 days old.
Cover your nose tightly
If you're too picky, you won't be able to use it.
Ah, now, now, now, wait a minute
Boy, really
How do you sit down?
Is it true?
Innacio
What a fun tune this is
After all, ours is good
No, is that so?
I like Shintobuli so much
Why are you stealing Seoguk’s items?
Did you miss this younger brother so much?
Is this what you followed me here?
How dare you take my watch
Intercept it and run to Cheongguk?
If you secretly extend it for a month
Did you think I would forgive you?
It's not yours, it's mine.
I bought it with my own money.
That's what I ordered!
Hey, did you forget?
A long-standing rule between you and me
Whoever takes it first gets it.
No, my brother too
My telescope last time
Didn't you intercept it?
Don't smirk
Bring it now
Write, that
It's broken
No, it's not that expensive
Why does it break so easily?
That thing is breaking
My heart too
I thought it was breaking
Baby, what should I do?
Get out quickly, quickly, quickly.
-Does this make me want to die?
- Brother
I won't be able to keep it properly
Why did you take it!
I went and got it
Five years have passed
Still haven't noticed the smoke?
Damn, acting is so difficult
Can’t you fake a left injury?
My natural elegance...
no
We are the greatest
You're a fool
A childish child and a brat
He is a fool himself.
The left injury is very suspicious.
It's a lot, yeah
Hey, give me the knife, okay?
Hey, you son of a bitch, Mr.
you me really
Shall I do the sword dance, huh?
don't worry too much
If I dance the sword dance, it's only
It will become a dance floor for the sitting table.
Be sure to cut off the head of the person sitting in the chair
About poverty and poverty
will take revenge
A month ago, the Crown Prince
Precious items brought from the Qing Dynasty
It seems that Prince Jeun has intercepted it.
Avoid the crown prince's anger
I think I went to the palace for a month.
at best
fighting over toys
They are childish.
Why are you so wary?
Genghis Khan's driving force
It was my father's revenge.
What is the crown prince
Even Genghis Khan
Are you saying it will work?
The crown prince lost his widow
King Jeun’s mother
I made you a ghost
They both must have had a grudge against me.
Just as there is no strength as strong as doubt,
As much as revenge
There are no strong weapons
Well, don't think about doing anything foolish.
This, this, work, working, work
Ah, I'm working...
Give me my clothes, give me my clothes
No, Yuna
Why are you...
Catch me, me, that gisaeng, okay?
- Damn it, Mr.
- That gisaeng, that gisaeng, that gisaeng
Jeundaegun Nari Myeongyo
Get out of the way
Get out of my way, get out of my way, get out of my way
Oh my, oh my
Oh, ah...
Catch that gisaeng
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Please catch that gisaeng!
Is this my name, Lord Jeundae, yes?
Please catch that gisaeng.
Uh...
Ugh
a c
Please catch that gisaeng.
Ah!
If you look closely at the stamina of a backpacker,
A big nose injury
- ho
- Oh my, why are you there...
Hey, wait a minute.
- Don't push.
- Leave it to me, leave it to me, leave it to me
Baby, baby...
Mr. Lee
If you look closely at this wanderer's obsession, it's very
It hurts my nose a lot
- Mr. A
- Stop it.
Please stop, you're right
Oh no
Well, it’s not that big of a deal.
Oh, the moon
Why can’t Gya go to Hanyang?
Well, I suddenly became curious.
The rising chaff
Didn't I tell you?
He is a slave who ran away from Hanyang.
There are still scoundrels
Looking for the moon
Ugh, that, over there.
To be honest, take a look
The moon is gone
You're not just a slave
What is it really?
Decoction
Did Dal go to Hanyang?
No
Hanyang is Musin
I went to Pyongyang, Pyongyang
keep in mind
The moon is never
You must not go to Hanyang
Come on by, Mr. Ai.
Me, me, me, me
If I fall here again
I could die, okay?
Oh, don't move, really.
If you come obediently now
To our Prince Jeundae, I am
I'll keep it a secret, okay?
‘Jeundaegun’?
If it's a large army...
Was the person who brought me here Wangchin?
If it's just Wang Chin
Fortunately?
His Majesty the late King
You are the only legitimate son, huh?
No, but
No matter how dirty this place is
Why is there so much fuss?
Boy, really, Mr.
If you don't come now, I
We will all reach our King Jeun.
Huh?
Rather than die
Mr. I
Huh?
What happens to him?
die
Your Majesty
You will be punished
You need to escape quickly, mama.
no one
Recognizing the child
No way
I missed you, madam.
Oh my!
Did you have parents?
- Since when?
- It's been there since birth.
If you catch the fallen petals
Do you know what happens?
If you catch the falling petals...
It's probably a serious matter
I feel like I'm caught up
Put this down
Let go of this!
If I solve this problem
Where is he?
Will you answer me?
Where are you, that kid!